Hey!
嘿！
How are you?
你好吗？
I'm okay, just calm down.
我没事，冷静一下。
Good.
好的。
The address you mean
你说的地址
I'll note it first.
我先记一下。
Good.
好的。
I already know.
我已经知道了。
Until found.
直到被发现。
Did Jiang Zhaoguo call just now?
Did Jiang Zhaoguo call just now?
Above this
上面这个
what is the address of Zhao country?
赵国的地址是什么？
This number is 45A3-8
这个号码是45A3-8
collected from military commanders.
从军事指挥官那里收集的。
Due to the habits of previous report senders
由于之前举报人的习惯
causes wear on the power cable
导致电源线磨损
so the examiner can see these characteristics
这样考官就可以看到这些特征
differentiate this message.
区分此消息。
Send from
发送自
45a3-8.
45a3-8。
Owned by Han Lu.
属于韩露。
Didn't think so, did you?
没想到吧？
We meet again.
我们再见面。
Why smoke so much?
为什么抽这么多烟？
Flustered?
心慌？
Why?
为什么？
Smoking is also not allowed?
也不允许吸烟吗？
On what basis did you arrest me?
你们凭什么逮捕我？
You are the one who conspired with the Chongqing government,
你就是与重庆政府合谋的人，
why didn't I catch you?
我为什么没抓住你？
Saying I colluded with the Chongqing government.
说我与重庆政府勾结。
Do you have any evidence?
你有证据吗？
Jiang Zhaoguo itu siapamu?
Jiang Zhaoguo itu siapamu?
We used to be friends
我们曾经是朋友
but haven't seen each other for a long time
但已经很久没见面了
is this also wrong?
这也错了吗？
We got the right information.
我们得到了正确的信息。
Jiang Zhaoguo baru tiba di Shanghai.
Jiang Zhaoguo baru tiba di Shanghai.
To look for you.
来寻找你。
No.
不。
You help him rent a house.
你帮他租房子。
You said he never looked for you?
你说他从来没有找过你？
Does renting a house mean he's ever looking for me?
租房子就代表他一直在找我吗？
Still don't want to admit it.
还是不愿意承认。
You are much more cunning than we imagine.
你比我们想象的要狡猾得多。
You know we follow you,
你知道我们跟着你，
so you don't let Jiang Zhaoguo
so you don't let Jiang Zhaoguo
come to your rental house
来你的出租屋
and for the sake of annoying
为了烦人
and misled our investigation
并误导了我们的调查
looking for someone to impersonate Jiang Zhaoguo.
找人冒充蒋兆国。
You're still pretending you're making preparations for negotiations
你还在假装正在为谈判做准备
right, right?
是的是的？
But you didn't expect that, did you?
但你没想到会这样，是吗？
Our people...
我们的人...
Brought home the original photo of Jiang Zhaoguo
把蒋兆国的原照片带回家
membawa foto asli Jiang Zhaoguo.
membawa foto asli Jiang Zhaoguo.
All this you said
这一切都是你说的
just your guess.
只是你的猜测。
Guess?
猜测？
You see this.
你看到这个了。
Not strange, right?
不奇怪吧？
You wrote it, right? Fuxu Road.
是你写的吧？府胥路。
Menurutku, Jiang Zhaoguo...
Menurutku, Jiang Zhaoguo...
It should be in this place now
现在应该在这个地方
what's the back?
后面是什么？
There isn't any.
没有。
The specific address,
具体地址，
say
说
I am a friend of the soldiers at the foot of the mountain.
我是山下战士的朋友。
You are like that to me,
你对我来说就是这样
you will definitely regret it.
你一定会后悔的。
Still going to practice martial arts?
还去练武吗？
A fighter at the foot of the mountain was dead.
山下一名战士已经死了。
Even if he is still alive,
即使他还活着，
can't help you either.
也帮不了你。
Say it or not?
说还是不说？
It's okay not to say it.
不说也没关系。
Fuxu Street only had so many buildings.
府胥街的建筑就这么多。
Feng Qi.
Feng Qi.
Look for places one by one,
一一寻找地方，
sampai menemukan Jiang Zhaoguo.
sampai menemukan Jiang Zhaoguo.
OK, I'll do it now.
好的，我现在就做。
You protect the country of Zhao.
你保护赵国。
Do you think it's appropriate?
你觉得合适吗？
Do you think he will protect you?
你觉得他会保护你吗？
We have a way to make him talk,
我们有办法让他说话
and tell him to comment on you.
并告诉他对你发表评论。
Once proven
一旦证明
Your crime is conspiring with the Chongqing government.
你的罪行是与重庆市政府合谋。
I'll cut...
我来剪...
To cut your pretty face.
来剪掉你漂亮的脸蛋。
So beautiful.
如此美丽。
Nona Zuo.
Nona Zuo.
It's okay, he passed out.
没事，他昏过去了。
Have you received a telegram from me?
你收到我的电报了吗？
Correct.
正确的。
I'll be there soon.
我很快就会到。
What's wrong with you, Miss Zuo?
左小姐你怎么了？
Help me break the iron chains.
帮我挣断铁链。
Good.
好的。
Look on the deck for a hammer or something.
在甲板上寻找锤子或其他东西。
Bai Qian.
Bai Qian.
where is he
他在哪里
Bai Qian, bangun.
Bai Qian, bangun.
What is this?
这是什么？
Looks like he fell asleep.
看来他睡着了。
Fall asleep.
睡着。
The ship is about to sail.
船即将起航。
What sleep?
睡什么？
here, wake up, here.
在这里，醒来，在这里。
Don't sleep anymore, Bai Qian.
白浅，别再睡了。
Do not move.
不要动。
Place high.
放置高处。
The left peach continues to use you.
左边的桃子继续使用你。
Didn't you realize that?
你没有意识到吗？
What does it have to do with you
跟你有什么关系
I do.
我愿意。
Stupid!
愚蠢的！
Do you know what you are doing?
你知道你在做什么吗？
Of course I know.
我当然知道。
Give me the key.
把钥匙给我。
Give him the key.
把钥匙给他。
Good
好的
You are destroying your future.
你正在毁掉你的未来。
Maybe my future
也许我的未来
contrary to you.
与你相反。
Defeat
打败
go quickly
快去
then when did you realize he was missing?
那你什么时候发现他失踪了？
About
关于
around 10 o'clock
10点左右
Today the weather is cold.
今天天气很冷。
I went to knock on the door
我去敲门
Want to ask whether it is necessary to use a mattress and blanket.
想问一下是否需要使用床垫和毯子。
Knocking for so long also no answer.
敲了这么久也没有回应。
I opened the door,
我已经开门了，
and realized there was no one there.
并意识到那里没有人。
Good, go.
好，走吧。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Go to his house to have a look.
去他家看看。
Road.
路。
Unexpectedly they use this kind of method
没想到他们竟然用这种方法
treat their people
对待他们的人民
changes really fast.
变化真的很快。
After experiencing these two days' things,
经历了这两天的事情后，
makes me feel
让我觉得
the border between friend and enemy
朋友与敌人的边界
suddenly became blurry
突然变得模糊
You say,
你说，
before I was your enemy,
在我成为你的敌人之前
now you are friends.
现在你们是朋友了。
However, if I were your friend,
不过，如果我是你的朋友，
aren't we both?
我们不是吗？
no more possibilities?
没有更多的可能性了吗？
So for me,
所以对我来说，
I'm afraid being an enemy would be better.
恐怕成为敌人会更好。
Previously I underestimated Chen Jia Ping too much.
以前我太低估陈家平了。
Last night if it wasn't for him
昨晚如果不是他
I will be a sinner.
我将成为一个罪人。
You clearly don't want to harm me,
你显然不想伤害我
but why do you always force me
但为什么你总是强迫我
threatened me
威胁我
do you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Drink coffee.
喝咖啡。
A warm body
温暖的身体
because Chen Jia Ping had changed the secret letter
因为陈家平改了密信
then your identity
那么你的身份
His identity to you?
他对你的身份？
He just didn't want Zhao An to find trouble with me.
他只是不想让赵安找我的麻烦而已。
I think it's your coffee
我想这是你的咖啡
much tastier than the ones sold at Kedai Kopi
比 Kedai Kopi 卖的好吃多了
better
更好的
then after the war is over,
那么战争结束后，
I just opened a coffee shop
我刚开了一家咖啡店
the business must be very good
生意一定很好
but open a coffee shop alone
却独自开一家咖啡店
still too lonely
还是太孤独
Today
今天
really don't know how to thank you
真不知道该如何感谢你
You previously really wanted to kill me.
你之前是真想杀了我。
Actually, you're not evil.
其实你并不邪恶。
No, I'm very evil.
不，我很邪恶。
I'm selfish.
我很自私。
Lonely.
孤独。
Paranoia.
偏执狂。
Is a person who legalizes all means to achieve his goal.
是一个为了达到目的而使一切手段合法化的人。
I feel
我觉得
you're just immature,
你只是不成熟
like a grown man.
像一个成年人一样。
Don't know
不知道
how to get what I want.
如何得到我想要的东西。
That's because I know,
那是因为我知道，
I can't get what I want
我无法得到我想要的
that's why I did something bad.
这就是我做了坏事的原因。
Correct
正确的
this transmitter
这个发射器
do you want me to move it back
你想让我把它移回来吗
I want you to help me send a telegram
我要你帮我发个电报
to your boss
给你的老板
so you have to use a transmitter
所以你必须使用发射器
Correct
正确的
but I don't have a password book.
但我没有密码本。
Inside this box are some messages after transcription
这个盒子里面是转录后的一些消息
and written text after translation.
以及翻译后的书面文本。
Using the cross comparison method
使用交叉比较法
give me one night,
给我一晚，
I can do it.
我能做到。
Trust you,
相信你，
Han Lu should have returned.
韩露应该已经回来了。
Then captured again by Zhao An's people.
然后又被赵安的人俘虏了。
Have warned him many times,
已经警告过他很多次了，
why do you still want to come back?
为什么你还想回来？
probably waiting for an important call
可能正在等待一个重要的电话
Already.
已经。
Nona Zuo.
Nona Zuo.
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Did I wake you up?
我吵醒你了吗？
No.
不。
Has it worked?
有效果吗？
Correct.
正确的。
This is a bunch of random ciphers.
这是一堆随机密码。
Based on a single table,
基于单个表，
enter mathematical formulas.
输入数学公式。
Make different words the same size
使不同的单词大小相同
achieve the goal of disrupting the opponent's analysis
达到扰乱对手分析的目的
but, this chaos numbers
但是，这个混乱的数字
not an unlimited number.
不是无限数量。
Usually
通常
add an old poem instead.
添加一首古诗代替。
This is for people
这是给人们的
who do not master the password pattern,
不掌握密码模式的人，
did have some confusion.
确实有些困惑。
But before,
但之前，
master the comparison of secret text and clear text.
掌握密文与明文的比较。
I found
我发现
this rule.
这条规则。
For me, it's resolved.
对我来说，已经解决了。
All this you say,
你说的这一切，
I do not quite understand.
我不太明白。
However, I feel...
不过，我觉得...
You're so great.
你太棒了。
Now it's very good
现在已经很好了
You can now send a report to your superior.
您现在可以向上级发送报告。
But
但
I understand.
我明白。
This is a secret.
这是一个秘密。
I can't be there.
我不能在那儿。
I'm going to work first.
我先去上班了。
Thank You.
谢谢。
After this,
在这之后，
will still come to do business again, okay?
还是会再来做生意的，好吗？
Very good.
非常好。
Can still see you.
还能见到你。
Go ahead
前进
Are you sure you've looked everywhere
你确定你到处都看过吗
we are some policemen who disguise themselves as concession house custodians
我们是一些伪装成特许屋管理员的警察
under the pretext of investigating a wanted criminal
以调查通缉犯为借口
already looking everywhere on Fuxu street,
已经在府胥街上四处张望，
but did not find Jiang Zhaoguo.
but did not find Jiang Zhaoguo.
Fuxu Road these three words,
福煦路这三个字，
Are you sure it was written by Han Lu?
你确定是韩露写的？
when answering the phone?
接电话时？
Not wrong.
没有错。
Now I
现在我
want to report to the Mu Village Chief.
想要向木村长汇报。
I think today there can be a breakthrough.
我想今天可能会有突破。
Now go also scolded.
现在走还骂。
Wait for me to come back,
等我回来
I'll check this frost.
我会检查一下这个霜。
Good.
好的。
Now where is he locked up?
现在他被关在哪里了？
And in the warehouse parking lot behind.
就在后面的仓库停车场。
No one will ever know.
没有人会知道。
After all, Han Lu is a star,
毕竟韩露是明星，
the influence is big.
影响力很大。
So that the brothers look after him,
为了让兄弟们照顾他，
no one can know
没有人能知道
he was locked up there.
他被锁在那里。
Understand
理解
stay cool.
保持冷静。
Fuxu Road is not Jiang Zhaoguo's country address,
府胥路不是蒋兆国的乡下地址，
I've said it from the start,
我从一开始就说过了
I don't know at all
我根本不知道
di mana Jiang Zhaoguo berada.
di mana Jiang Zhaoguo berada.
You guys are carelessly guessing.
你们胡乱猜测吧。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
You touch it.
你触摸它。
let me go
让我走
Have you touched it?
你摸过吗？
Are there round scars?
有圆形疤痕吗？
You know what that is?
你知道那是什么吗？
This was shot
这是被拍的
on the forehead for five minutes
放在额头上五分钟
Only then can a round trace appear this deep.
只有这样，圆形的痕迹才会出现这么深。
If I can't find Jiang Zhaoguo,
If I can't find Jiang Zhaoguo,
shot in my forehead
我的额头中弹
will fire bullets
会发射子弹
exploded in my head
在我的脑海中爆炸
put out thoughts
提出想法
where is the country of Zhao?
赵国在哪里？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Have you forgotten what I said yesterday?
你忘记我昨天说的话了吗？
I will cut off your faces one by one
我会把你的脸一张一张地砍下来
your beautiful face
你美丽的脸庞
feng Qi.
feng Qi.
I asked one last time.
我上次问过一次。
Di mana Jiang Zhaoguo?
Di mana Jiang Zhaoguo?
I don't know.
我不知道。
Loud mouth
大声说话
let go.
松手。
This is your last chance.
这是你最后的机会。
Really don't want to say?
真的不想说吗？
Grumpy Girl,
脾气暴躁的女孩，
bite me!
咬我！
I made you unable to act anymore.
我让你无法再行动了。
Stop it!
停下来！
Zhao An.
Zhao An.
You really have big guts!
你胆子还真大啊！
You've been brave for a few days,
这几天你很勇敢
These are police from the Military Police Headquarters.
这些是宪兵总部的警察。
Naoki,
直树，
good morning sir
早上好先生
Specially came for Miss Han Lu's matter.
特意来找韩露小姐的事的。
When he was dying,
当他快要死的时候，
surrender all
放弃一切
it's all on Lord Zhongzuo.
一切都在忠佐君身上。
Especially telling me
特别告诉我
to take good care of Miss Han Lu.
照顾好韩露小姐。
Good.
好的。
Kapten Ueda,
上田卡普顿,
we suspect,
我们怀疑，
owned by Han Lu,
韩璐拥有，
colluded with Chongqing to represent Jiang Zhaoguo's country.
勾结重庆代表蒋兆国国家。
Do you have any proof?
你有什么证据吗？
Ada.
艾达.
What I said is strong evidence.
我说的都是有力的证据。
You're not the one who always creates fake news.
你不是那个总是制造假新闻的人。
Of course.
当然。
Is it actually there or not?
它实际上存在还是不存在？
Ada.
艾达.
Still dodging.
还在躲。
Miss Han Lu, are you okay?
韩露小姐，你还好吗？
He's okay.
他没事。
We're just getting started.
我们才刚刚开始。
Quickly release Miss Han Lu.
赶紧放了韩露小姐。
Good.
好的。
Let go.
松手。
Sini, sini Tuan Zhongzuo.
Sini, sini Tuan Zhongzuo.
Come here please.
请过来这里。
He is very brave.
他非常勇敢。
To go to Taihe Company.
前往太和公司。
Good.
好的。
Here.
这里。
Miss Han Lu, are you okay?
韩露小姐，你还好吗？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Thank you very much, Nita.
非常感谢你，妮塔。
Rancid Girl, you're quite cruel.
臭丫头，你太残忍了。
Chief.
首席。
Naoki Neta.
奈塔直树.
How did he know we captured Han Lu?
他怎么知道我们抓到了韩露？
Still ask me.
还是问我吧。
Someone must have done it.
一定有人做到了。
How is section chief Chen?
陈科长怎么样？
qian Xiu Cai
qian Xiu Cai
section chief Chen
陈科长
Has the magazine I ordered arrived?
我订购的杂志到了吗？
What magazine?
什么杂志？
Xin Guang.
Xin Guang.
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
Why have you been interested lately?
为什么你最近感兴趣？
see this beautiful girl's painting?
看到这位美丽女孩的画了吗？
Isn't it because recently...
是不是因为最近...
The cover is the famous artist Miss Han Lu?
封面是著名艺术家韩露小姐？
OK, I'll find it for you.
好的，我给你找一下。
Have found.
已经发现。
I've found it, I've found it.
我找到了，我找到了。
Come section chief Chen
来陈科长吧
qian Xiu Cai
qian Xiu Cai
do you think this Miss Han Lu,
你觉得这位韩露小姐，
Is everything you see good?
你看到的一切都好吗？
I'm just looking.
我只是随便看看。
How can you admire a great artist like this?
这样一位伟大的艺术家，你怎么能欣赏呢？
My job is to guard the door.
我的工作是守门。
No need to look at the big artists.
没必要看大艺术家。
OK, I'll go first.
好的，我先走了。
You said this magazine cover is still alive?
你说这本杂志封面还活着？
Owned by Han Lu.
属于韩露。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
Don't make a fuss.
别小题大做。
Look who's here.
你看谁在这儿啊。
Kapten Ueda.
上田卡普顿.
I'm a fan of Miss Han Lu.
我是韩露小姐的粉丝。
I don't know if I can or not.
我不知道我能不能。
Ask Miss Han Lu to sign for me.
请韩露小姐帮我签收。
It's okay, I'll help you sign it.
没关系，我帮你签字。
Very fast.
非常快。
Owned by Han Lu.
属于韩露。
He must have loved it
他一定很喜欢
the film played by Miss Han Lu.
该片由韩露小姐饰演。
Thank you for contacting Naeda.
感谢您联系苗田。
Yapei Road number 72,
亚培路72号
hey!
嘿！
How about you?
你呢？
I've found a home.
我已经找到家了
Those guys didn't make trouble with you later, right?
后来那些家伙没有找你麻烦吧？
I'm okay, just calm down.
我没事，冷静一下。
Good.
好的。
The address you mean
你说的地址
I'll note it first.
我先记一下。
Number 72, Jalan Yapet.
72 号，Jalan Yapet。
Fine, I know.
好吧，我知道。
Until found.
直到被发现。
Thank you Miss Han Lu.
谢谢韩露小姐。
Two o'clock in the afternoon.
下午两点。
What did you say?
你说什么？
Miss Han Lu is very weak.
韩露小姐身体很虚弱。
Don't bother him.
别打扰他。
Good.
好的。
Take Miss Han Lu to my car.
送韩露小姐到我的车上。
I took him to the hospital.
我带他去了医院。
Good.
好的。
Here.
这里。
Hurry up.
赶快。
Slowly.
慢慢地。
Heart
心
Good.
好的。
Later look for me in my office.
稍后到我办公室来找我。
What is it?
它是什么？
These two Japanese
这两个日本人
now in Shanghai,
现在在上海，
are you able
你可以
find them out
找出他们
who are these two people?
这两个人是谁？
The background of this problem is very complicated.
这个问题的背景非常复杂。
The reason why Zhao An forced him to confess to Han Lu
赵安逼迫他向韩露表白的原因
is also related to this.
也与此有关。
Now Zhao An has lost,
现在赵安已经输了，
our chance has come.
我们的机会来了。
Jalan Yapet No. 72,
雅佩路 (Jalan Yapet) 号 72、
Please come in.
请进来。
Section Chief Chen.
陈科长.
Feng Qi brothers
冯琪兄弟
his hand was slightly injured
他的手受了轻伤
Want to go to the hospital.
想去医院。
My brother.
我的兄弟。
This is not a small wound,
这可不是一个小伤口，
have to go quickly.
必须快点走。
Small wound, small wound.
小伤口，小伤口。
This is because
这是因为
looking for you to open the injury confirmation letter.
找你打开受伤确认信。
I've only just been able to receive public funds.
我刚刚能够收到公共资金。
Just got to the hospital.
刚到医院。
Understand.
理解。
You talk about these officials,
你谈论这些官员，
making this a vague formality
使这成为一种模糊的形式
truly.
真的。
If we get shot while on duty,
如果我们在执勤时被枪杀
After returning, you have to fill in the form before you can be saved.
回来后必须填写表格才可以保存。
Ridiculous
荒谬的
all this bureaucracy
所有这些官僚机构
will be delayed.
会被延迟。
How did you get hurt?
你是怎么受伤的？
Han Lu was bitten by a smelly woman.
韩露被臭女人咬了。
Han Lu.
Han Lu.
Sorry, section chief Chen.
对不起，陈科长。
I forgot you're a Han Lu fan.
我忘了你是韩露粉丝了
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Fans are fans.
粉丝就是粉丝。
Brothers are still brothers.
兄弟终究是兄弟。
How do you think it got hurt?
你觉得它是怎么受伤的？
Bitten by frost.
被霜冻咬伤了。
Sorry, my smelly mouth.
对不起，我的嘴很臭。
Sorry section chief Chen
对不起陈科长
brother Feng Qi
brother Feng Qi
we have to do it according to the rules
我们必须按照规则去做
what does it mean?
这是什么意思？
No rush.
不着急。
I'll turn it around for you.
我会为你扭转局面。
Article 4.
第 4 条。
Article 6.
第 6 条。
Here, here look.
来来来，看这里。
Article 7, point 3 regulates that
第 7 条第 3 点规定：
Work accidents are violence that occurs
工作事故是发生的暴力
violence due to work responsibilities,
由于工作职责而发生的暴力行为，
accidental injury, etc.
意外伤害等
Can be considered an injury at work.
可以视为工伤。
Correct.
正确的。
This is an on-the-job injury.
这是工伤。
But brother Feng Qi
不过风起哥哥
catching frost
捕捉霜
That is the personality of you and Captain Zhao.
这就是你和赵队长的性格。
Naoki Neta and Manager Luo
内塔直树和罗经理
don't agree.
不同意。
Of course it cannot be considered as carrying out official duties,
当然不能算是执行公务，
then it does not include work-related injuries.
那么不包括工伤。
Correct?
正确的？
If so, you mean,
如果是这样，你的意思是，
I was bitten in vain
我被白白咬了
brother Feng Qi
brother Feng Qi
I only acted fairly.
我只是表现得公平而已。
Chief Chen
陈科长
I feel like you kinda
我感觉你有点像
to take personal revenge on the company
对公司进行个人报复
brother Feng Qi
brother Feng Qi
Personal revenge in this company is not
在这家公司，个人报复是不存在的
ketua tim Zhao
ketua tim Zhao
leader
领导者
Wrong signature.
签名错误。
Captain Zhao, I'm really sorry.
赵队长，真的很抱歉。
It's all my fault for being careless.
都是我的不小心惹的祸。
Please go alone.
请你一个人去吧。
Next time you call me.
下次你打电话给我。
I will deliver it to you.
我会把它送给你。
No next time.
没有下次了。
Chief don't go
酋长别走
you came at the right time
你来得正是时候
try checking.
尝试检查。
Section Chief Chen did not think this was a work accident
陈科长并不认为这是一起工伤事故
brother Feng Qi
brother Feng Qi
if you really think I'm taking personal revenge on the company
如果你真的认为我是在对公司进行个人报复
You go find Manager Luo
你去找罗经理吧
or report to me at the Military Commander.
或者向我的军事指挥官报告。
Chairman Zhao, I am...
赵主席，我是...
I will act fairly.
我会公平行事。
Just a small wound
只是一个小伤口
couldn't he bandage wounds?
他不能包扎伤口吗？
He didn't identify a work accident for you,
他没有给你认定工伤事故，
pack it yourself.
自己打包吧。
OK, Captain.
好的，队长。
I'll wrap it myself.
我自己包一下。
I know how to wrap wounds.
我知道如何包扎伤口。
My ex-girlfriend, Xiao Fang, is studying in Japan.
我的前女友小芳在日本留学。
Captain Zhao, I'll bring it to you in a moment.
赵队长，我一会儿就给你拿过来。
He taught me.
他教了我。
I made it myself.
我自己做的。
Better than the hospital
比医院好
something happened, section chief Chen.
陈科长出事了。
The left twin wants to jump from the building.
左边的双胞胎想从大楼跳下去。
Left twin peaches want to jump off the building!
左双桃子想跳楼！
Liuli Guoguo.
Liuli Guoguo.
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Hurry down
快点下来
chen Jia Ping
chen Jia Ping
do you want to divorce me?
你想和我离婚吗？
If you want to divorce me
如果你想和我离婚
then I'll jump.
那我就跳了。
What's the problem, we'll talk about it again after we go downstairs.
有什么问题，我们下楼再说。
Don't come here.
别来这里。
In the future
将来
Good.
好的。
I'm not here.
我不在这儿。
What is the problem
问题是什么
we go down anyway can talk
无论如何我们下去可以谈谈
It's fine if I go down.
如果我下去就好了。
You apologize first.
你先道歉。
Why should I apologize?
我为什么要道歉？
You were the one who wronged me first.
你才是第一个冤枉我的人。
You hit me?
你打我？
I'm an adult
我是成年人了
no one ever hit me
从来没有人打过我
and you're very heavy
你很重
Until now my face here still hurts.
直到现在我的脸还疼。
Why are you coming home?
你为什么要回家？
You don't want to apologize, do you?
你不想道歉，是吗？
Do you want to apologize or not?
你想道歉还是不想道歉？
Fine.
美好的。
can i apologize
我可以道歉吗
It's all my fault.
都是我的错。
This is all my fault.
这都是我的错。
I shouldn't have slapped you.
我不应该打你一巴掌。
I am wrong.
我错了。
Come down
坠落
here.
这里。
Come down.
坠落。
This can't be done.
这是不可能的。
You're the only one apologizing.
你是唯一一个道歉的人。
This is both of our problems
这是我们俩的问题
who else apologized to you?
还有谁向你道歉？
I...
我...
I'm humble.
我很谦虚。
I used a letter to threaten Miss Zuo
我用信威胁左小姐
so this problem occurs.
所以就会出现这个问题。
Sorry,
对不起，
but i hope
但我希望
You shouldn't leave the company because of this.
你不应该因此而离开公司。
Because here,
因为在这里，
someone needs you.
有人需要你。
I mean is
我的意思是
Section Chief Chen.
陈科长.
Liuli Guoguo.
Liuli Guoguo.
The person who should apologize, has already apologized to you.
该道歉的人已经向你道歉了。
Don't make any more noise.
别再发出任何声音了。
Hurry down.
快点下来。
Can't.
不能。
There is still one more person who wants to apologize.
还有一个人想要道歉。
Yes, that's me.
是的，这就是我。
It is my fault.
这是我的错。
I am not good.
我不好。
I'm so careless.
我真是太不小心了。
And hurt you.
并伤害了你。
Hurt our feelings.
伤害我们的感情。
I do not want to lose you.
我不想失去你。
You are the only person I can rely on in my life.
你是我这辈子唯一可以依靠的人。
So...
所以...
My husband, please forgive me.
我的丈夫，请原谅我。
Give me...
给我吗...
Our love has one more chance.
我们的爱情还有一次机会。
Isn't that good?
这不是很好吗？
Everyone will make mistakes.
每个人都会犯错误。
Have you forgotten what you said at the wedding?
你忘了你在婚礼上说的话了吗？
Say.
说。
You're not perfect
你并不完美
I'm not perfect either
我也不完美
but...
但...
However, we are together...
然而，我们在一起...
It's perfect.
这是完美的。
Still remember.
还记得。
In that case,
在这种情况下，
let's get down together perfectly
让我们完美地在一起
Good?
好的？
Good.
好的。
But I still can't forgive you.
但我还是无法原谅你。
Little by little I want to die
渐渐地我想死
is a knowledgeable and cultured person.
是一个有知识、有文化的人。
Why are you such a fierce woman?
你怎么是个这么凶的女人？
You don't forgive me
你不原谅我
I still haven't forgiven you.
我还是没有原谅你。
Just now at the door,
刚才在门口，
why are you hugging the cold dew?
你为何拥抱着冰冷的露珠？
I didn't hug him.
我没有拥抱他。
He passed out, I'm daddy.
他昏倒了，我是爸爸。
How ridiculous.
多么可笑啊。
Seeing other people is not dizzy,
看别人不晕，
to meet you?
遇见你？
Still holding it for so long, not letting go.
还抱了那么久，不肯放开。
Do not let go.
不要放手。
Good.
好的。
I was wrong, I was wrong.
我错了，我错了。
Disband, disband.
解散，解散。
Let's have a meeting.
我们开个会吧。
Not meeting people.
不与人相见。
You guys are the ones who see the most commotion.
你们是最能看到骚动的人。
Recently.
最近。
What problem do you have?
你有什么问题吗？
Close the door, talk quietly.
关上门，小声说话。
Shooing away the ducks, go up to the stage.
赶走鸭子，上台。
Act like this.
像这样行事。
So that everyone feels that we are good again
让大家都觉得我们又好了
right, right?
是的是的？
You're good too.
你也很好。
The left twin peach is back.
左边的双桃又回来了。
Not just coming back,
不只是回来，
he also forced me to act with him in the shop.
他还强迫我在店里和他一起演戏。
Make him go away
让他走开
and why come back, this problem is solved
为什么回来，这个问题已经解决了
I'm thinking
我在想
whether it is military power
无论是军事实力
have any urgent tasks?
有什么紧急任务吗？
There is a possibility
有一种可能
maybe this time
也许这次
ready to lurk for a long time
准备长期潜伏
old way
老方法
this time don't think about telling me to leave again.
这次别再想着要我离开了。
I don't want to.
我不想。
This is not for you to determine
这不是由你决定的
I'm not the one who can determine.
我不是那个能决定的人。
This is an organizational decision.
这是一个组织决定。
Now the situation has changed
现在情况发生了变化
I'll have to ask the organization for instructions again
我得再次向组织请示
If that's the case, I'll write the request.
如果是这样的话，我会写下请求。
If the organization allows me to stay and continue scouting,
如果组织允许我留下来继续物色，
I can guarantee,
我可以保证，
will not affect
不会影响
affecting the security of my identity.
影响我的身份安全。
And my job.
还有我的工作。
I'll write now
我现在就写
I will use this inkstone
我要用这个砚台
Do not rush
不着急
even though you have written the application,
即使你已经写好了申请，
it takes time for the organization to agree.
该组织需要时间才能达成一致。
Now the most important thing is,
现在最重要的是，
because the Left Twin is back,
因为左双胞胎回来了，
How do you manage your relationship with him?
你如何处理和他的关系？
I feel,
我觉得，
if I pretend I don't know anything anymore,
如果我假装我什么都不知道
instead, it's like I'm covering something up.
相反，就像我在掩盖什么。
So it's better if I ask him directly.
所以我还是直接问他比较好。
After all, he's home,
毕竟他在家，
must have thought of a way to explain it to me.
一定是想办法向我解释一下。
So I will take advantage of it.
所以我会利用它。
Pretend to believe it, explain it to him.
假装相信，给他解释一下。
This is enough for the time being.
暂时这已经足够了。
It shouldn't be a problem either.
这应该也不是问题。
The old way
老办法
That secret letter was for you
那封秘密信是写给你的
has it been solved?
解决了吗？
Already.
已经。
Very valuable.
非常有价值。
Is a person
是一个人
who is hiding in Yan'an.
谁躲在延安。
With the code name Dayan from the General's spy.
代号大雁，来自将军的间谍。
There are military spies in Yan'an,
延安有军事特务，
is being examined in secret.
正在秘密审查中。
Reportedly there are still no results.
据报道，目前还没有结果。
Fill in the secret message
填写密文
related to the economic and financial conditions of Yan'an.
这与延安的经济金融状况有关。
It's not a secret story.
这不是一个秘密故事。
But the fighters
但战士们
because he attaches so much importance to this secret call,...
因为他对这次秘密通话如此重视，……
It shouldn't be about the content,
不应该是内容的问题
but this spy nicknamed Dayan
但这名间谍绰号“大雁”
big goose
大鹅
Pretty cool too.
也很酷。
Since when did you learn to cook?
你从什么时候开始学会做饭的？
You can always do that.
你总是可以这样做。
Why come back?
为什么回来？
I am your wife.
我是你的妻子。
Those two people,
那两个人，
I asked why did you come home?
我问你为什么回家？
Previously my company was in Wuhan
之前我的公司在武汉
has been dismissed.
已被解雇。
I don't have any work there,
我在那里没有任何工作
I'm better
我比较好
live in Shanghai,
住在上海，
accompany my husband.
陪伴我的丈夫。
Left twin.
左边双胞胎。
I asked again.
我又问了一遍。
Why did you come back?
你为什么回来？
Do you really have no feelings for me at all?
你真的对我一点感觉都没有吗？
Guoguo, haven't we both agreed?
果果，我们不是都同意了吗？
This way,
这边走，
is the best ending
是最好的结局
now you're home,
现在你回家了，
will bring a lot of trouble for us.
会给我们带来很多麻烦。
Don't you know?
你不知道吗？
I lost contact with my organization.
我与我的组织失去了联系。
What organization?
什么组织？
The team.
团队。
What is it?
它是什么？
Never saw the General.
没见过将军。
I've never met anyone still alive.
我从未见过还活着的人。
I'm joking with you.
我在跟你开玩笑。
How could it be military power?
怎么可能是军事力量呢？
My organization
我的组织
it's called the Soul Group.
它被称为灵魂团体。
I joined when I was in Wuhan.
我在武汉的时候就加入了。
What team?
什么队？
Just a few young people who love the country,
就几个热爱祖国的年轻人，
who wanted to do something to fight Japan and save the country.
他想为抗日救国做点什么。
Are you really not a commander?
你真的不是指挥官吗？
Really isn't it?
真的不是吗？
So the soldiers had killed very many,
所以士兵们杀了很多人，
look at me.
看着我。
Similar or not?
类似还是不类似？
Why don't you go back to Wuhan?
你为什么不回武汉？
Didn't I just say that?
我刚才不是说过了吗？
I lost contact with my organization.
我与我的组织失去了联系。
My boss disappeared.
我的老板失踪了。
So if I don't find it,
所以如果我没找到的话
I can't contact my organization.
我无法联系我的组织。
I don't believe it.
我不相信。
Of course you guys
当然你们
there's a new assignment, right?
有新任务了是吗？
Where are the new tasks?
新任务在哪里？
Our organization
我们的组织
everything is a minor fuss
一切都是小题大做
one hammer in the east and one stick in the west
东一锤，西一棒
can't do anything big
不能做任何大事
however,
然而，
is an anti-Japanese group, right?
是一个抗日团体吧？
If Lao Luo and Zhao An were found out,
如果老罗和赵安被发现的话
I became a member of an anti-Japanese family.
我成为了一个抗日家庭的一员。
Aren't you going to involve me?
你不打算连累我吗？
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
There are many organizations like us.
像我们这样的组织有很多。
So there are so many Middle Commanders
所以有这么多中层指挥官
Chinese Communist Party.
中共。
Can't be caught
无法被抓住
who will care about us?
谁会关心我们？
What did I involve you in?
我让你参与了什么？
Gao Fang also knows your identity.
高放也知道你的身份。
If you go,
如果你走的话，
there is no proof of his words.
他的话没有证据。
Now you're back,
现在你回来了，
what if he threatens you again?
如果他再次威胁你怎么办？
I guarantee he won't threaten me.
我保证他不会威胁我。
On what basis are you
你凭什么
why do you have so many questions?
你为什么有这么多问题？
Coward.
懦夫。
This doesn't look like you.
这看起来不像你。
Isn't it similar?
是不是很相似呢？
If you're scared,
如果你害怕的话
you would have taken such a big risk that day.
那天你会冒这么大的风险。
To help me at the cafe.
在咖啡馆帮我。
I am a person who has intelligence.
我是一个有智慧的人。
Now that I think about it
现在我想起来了
still sweating coldly
依然冷汗淋漓
don't know if you're really scared
不知道你是否真的害怕
or pretend to be afraid.
或假装害怕。
Of course I'm scared.
我当然害怕。
Even if you don't involve me,
就算你不让我参与，
if your organization knows about me,
如果您的组织了解我，
kill me to silence me?
杀了我让我闭嘴？
How about this?
这个怎么样？
Biggest case we've ever done
我们做过的最大的案例
is burning Wang Pu Jun's barn.
正在烧毁王朴军的谷仓。
Isn't killing me a bigger case?
杀了我不是更大的案子吗？
So you won't betray me, right?
所以你不会背叛我，对吗？
What if I betray you?
如果我背叛你怎么办？
Then I...
然后我...
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I will...
我会...
A storm.
一场风暴。
Don't.
不。
Then I'm more afraid.
那我就更害怕了。
It's good to be afraid.
感到害怕是件好事。
Good.
好的。
Left twin.
左边双胞胎。
I can not betray you.
我不能背叛你。
But you have to guarantee my safety.
但你要保证我的安全。
As long as you don't betray me,
只要你不背叛我
I not only guarantee your safety,
我不仅保证您的安全，
I'm still your wife.
我仍然是你的妻子。
Every day cooking for you.
每天给你做饭。
To be honest,
说实话，
when you see me again,
当你再次见到我时
do you feel a little happy?
你感到有点高兴吗？
No.
不。
I know,
我知道，
now you treat me with half sincerity.
现在你对我半点诚意。
Which is real and which is fake.
哪个是真的，哪个是假的。
The mouth is fake.
嘴巴是假的
The heart is genuine.
心是真诚的。
Eat a lot.
吃了很多。
Eat it.
吃了它。
Why? Afraid I'll poison him?
为什么？怕我毒死他吗？
I'll eat it for you too.
我也给你吃。
Not poison.
不是毒药。
But salty.
不过是咸的。
How about this?
这个怎么样？
Just delivered,
刚刚交付，
now it's back.
现在它回来了。
Judging from this attitude,
从这个态度来看，
is preparing to lurk for a long time
正准备长期潜伏
maybe because of this problem,
也许是因为这个问题，
then told me to go.
然后叫我走。
The worst thing is that there is still a mission tomorrow.
最糟糕的是明天还有任务。
Is there anything to do tomorrow?
明天有什么事情要做吗？
Tomorrow there are business matters.
明天还有生意上的事。
Still have business on Sunday?
周日还有生意吗？
It seems like being a traitor is also tiring.
看来当叛徒也很累啊。
I am a traitor who has ideals and ambitions.
我是一个有理想、有野心的叛徒。
How about you?
你呢？
What do you want to do tomorrow?
明天你想做什么？
My uncle is looking for me on business.
我叔叔正在找我出差。
Okay.
好的。
Tomorrow you'll just be busy with your business.
明天你就只忙你的事了。
I'm busy with my business.
我正忙着我的事。
Tomorrow at two o'clock in the afternoon,
明天下午两点，
Yer Pei Street Number 72,
叶培街 72 号，